# **Rachelle Adams**

770.881.2242 • adamsrachelle@icloud.com • linkedin.com/in/adamsrachelle

#### **PROFILE**

Diligent and articulate office administrator with the demonstrated capacity to learn skills quickly and apply them effectively. Possesses a keen aptitude for efficiency, organization, and communication. An instinctive leader and problem solver with over 10 years of experience assisting stakeholders at all levels.

## **EXPERIENCE**

# **Community Development Office Assistant**, City of Smyrna; Smyrna, GA — 2020–Present

- Facilitate processes related to city planning and development, construction review and permitting, business licensing, and code enforcement.
- Maintain knowledge of City's code of ordinances to accurately inform citizens.
- Schedule daily inspections for Chief Building Official and site inspectors.
- Prepare department status reports for City administration and constituents.
- Manage database information, physical records, supply inventory, and office organization.

# **Scheduling Coordinator**, Atlanta Arbor Tree Care Specialist; Marietta, GA — 2016–2020

- Managed production calendar to meet and exceed daily revenue goals.
- Responsible for route planning, equipment allocation, and timely scheduling of client projects.
- Organized and secured permitting to ensure compliance with local ordinances.
- Provided administrative support to company management.
- Served as front desk reception and first point of contact for clients and vendors.

## **Sales Manager**, Lane Bryant; Kennesaw, GA - 2014-2016

- Built and retained clientele through consultative sales and product expertise.
- Trained staff in customer service and operational best practices to drive positive KPI results.
- Analyzed store performance data to identify sales opportunities and develop team strengths.
- Managed back-office administration to comply with monthly audits.
- Promoted from Sales Associate in October 2014.

## **Floor Manager**, Garden Ridge; Kennesaw, GA – 2012–2014

- Supervised sales floor and 15+ sales associates for high-volume retail warehouse.
- Managed customer service and visual merchandising to improve guest experience.
- Trained new hires in warehouse safety procedures to comply with OSHA standards.
- Performed clerical duties to support upper management in fast-paced environment.
- Promoted from Sales Associate in January 2013.

# **EDUCATION**

## Kennesaw State University, Michael J. Coles College of Business; Kennesaw, GA

 $\bullet$  Bachelor of Business Administration in Economics, Minor in Film Studies -2012

## **SKILLS**

Office Management, Project Management, Data Entry, Data Analysis, Research, Customer Service, Team Leadership, Employee Development & Training, Content Creation, Social Media, Windows, macOS, Microsoft Office, Apple iWork, Google G Suite, QuickBooks